Guide to the Laura McPhee River of No Return Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Material, 2003–2008; Series I
  - Work Prints, 2003–2008
    - Chromogenic Color Prints, 2003–2008
      - Images Captured in 2003
        - Negative Number 6110, Varient 1, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 332)
        - Negative Number 6110, Varient 2, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 333)
        - Negative Number 6111, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 334)
        - Negative Numbers 6113 to 6123, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 335-345)
        - Negative Numbers 6253 to 6254, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 346-347)
        - Negative Numbers 6540 to 6548, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 348-356)
        - Negative Numbers 6550 to 6553, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 357-360)
        - Negative Numbers 6574 to 6575, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 361-362)
        - Negative Numbers 6578 to 6580, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 363-365)
        - Negative Numbers 6583, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 366)
        - Negative Numbers 6584-1520, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 367)
        - Negative Number 6587, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 368)
        - Negative Number 6589, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 369)
        - Negative Number 6591, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 370)
        - Negative Number 6591, Varient 1, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 371)
        - Negative Numbers 6597 to 6604, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 372-379)
        - Negative Numbers 6606 to 6608, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 380-382)
        - Negative Numbers 7545 to 7546, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 383-384)
        - Negative Number 7549, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 385)
        - Negative Numbers 7551 to 7559, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 386-394)
        - Negative Numbers 7602 to 7615, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 395-408)
        - Negative Numbers 7754 to 7760, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 409-415)
        - Negative Number 7761, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 416)
        - Negative Numbers 7762-7763, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 417-418)
        - Negative Number 7821, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 419)
        - Negative Numbers 7853 to 7865, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 420-432)
        - Negative Numbers 7890 to 7899, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 433-442)
        - Negative Numbers 7902 to 7909, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 443-450)
        - Negative Numbers 8001 to 8002, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 451-452)
        - Negative Numbers 8004 to 8013, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 453-462)
        - Negative Numbers 8015 to 8016, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 463-464)
        - Negative Number 8018, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 465)
        - Negative Numbers 8020 to 8034, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 466-480)
        - Negative Number 8036, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 481)
        - Negative Numbers 8038 to 8039, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 482-483)
        - Negative Numbers 8043 to 8044, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 484-485)
        - Negative Number 8047, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 486)
        - Negative Numbers 8059 to 8060, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 487-488)
        - Negative Numbers 8074 to 8078, printed 2003 September (Box 16, Folder 489-493)
      - Images Captured in 2004
        - Negative Numbers 9555 to 9574, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 494-513)
        - Negative Number 9609, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 514)
        - Negative Numbers 9633 to 9651, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 515-533)
        - Negative Numbers 9653 to 9655, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 534-536)
        - Negative Numbers 9657 to 9660, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 537-540)
        - Negative Numbers 9722 to 9726, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 541-545)
        - Negative Numbers 9728 to 9731, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 546-549)
        - Negative Numbers 9733 to 9739, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 550-556)
        - Negative Numbers 9741 to 9750, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 557-566)
        - Negative Number 9752, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 567)
        - Negative Number 9753, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 568)
        - Negative Numbers 9754 to 9756, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 569-571)
        - Negative Numbers 9766 to 9783, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 572-589)
        - Negative Numbers 9785 to 9788, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 590-593)
        - Negative Numbers 9792 to 9794, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 594-596)
        - Negative Numbers 9808 to 9809, printed 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 597-598)
        - Negative Numbers 1890 to 1892, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 599-601)
        - Negative Numbers 3166 to 3170, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 602-606)
        - Negative Numbers 4001 to 4007, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 607-613)
        - Negative Numbers 6340 to 6357, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 614-631)
        - Negative Numbers 6379 to 6383, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 632-636)
        - Negative Numbers 6385 to 6441, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 637-693)
        - Negative Numbers 6448 to 6452, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 694-698)
        - Negative Numbers 6454 to 6468, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 699-713)
        - Negative Numbers 6471 to 6475, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 714-718)
        - Negative Numbers 6478 to 6505, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 719-746)
        - Negative Numbers 6507 to 6521, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 747-761)
        - Negative Numbers 6523 to 6536, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 762-775)
        - Negative Number 6584, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 776)
        - Negative Number 6585, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 777)
        - Negative Numbers 6586 to 6587, printed 2004 June (Box 18, Folder 778-779)
        - Negative Numbers 2912 to 2929, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 780-797)
        - Negative Number 2932, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 798)
        - Negative Numbers 2935 to 2936, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 799-800)
        - Negative Numbers 2938 to 2941, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 801-804)
        - Negative Numbers 2943 to 2944, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 805-806)
        - Negative Number 2951, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 807)
        - Negative Numbers 2954 to 2958, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 808-812)
        - Negative Numbers 2961 to 2967, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 813-819)
        - Negative Numbers 2969 to 2973, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 820-824)
        - Negative Numbers 2975 to 2984, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 825-834)
        - Negative Numbers 2986 to 2987, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 835-836)
        - Negative Number 2989, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 837)
        - Negative Numbers 2992 to 2993, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 838-839)
        - Negative Number 2995, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 840)
        - Negative Numbers 2998 to 3012, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 841-855)
        - Negative Numbers 3014 to 3022, printed 2004 November (Box 19, Folder 856-864)
      - Images Captured in 2005
        - Negative Numbers 626 to 633, printed 2005 March (Box 20, Folder 865-872)
        - Negative Numbers 636 to 639, printed 2005 March (Box 20, Folder 873-876)
        - Negative Numbers 641 to 669, printed 2005 March (Box 20, Folder 877-905)
        - Negative Numbers 671 to 674, printed 2005 March (Box 20, Folder 906-909)
        - Negative Number 677, printed 2005 March (Box 20, Folder 910)
        - Negative Numbers 680 to 684, printed 2005 March (Box 20, Folder 911-915)
        - Negative Numbers 686 to 698, printed 2005 March (Box 20, Folder 916-928)
        - Negative Numbers 710 to 720, printed 2005 March (Box 20, Folder 929-939)
        - Negative Numbers 2070 to 2078, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 940-948)
        - Negative Number 2079, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 949)
          Print printed backwards.
        - Negative Numbers 2080 to 2081, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 950-951)
        - Negative Numbers 2083 to 2084, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 952-953)
        - Negative Numbers 2086 to 2104, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 954-972)
        - Negative Numbers 2106 to 2127, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 973-994)
        - Negative Numbers 2129 to 2135, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 995-1001)
        - Negative Numbers 2139 to 2140, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 1002-1003)
        - Negative Numbers 2142 to 2148, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 1004-1010)
        - Negative Number 2508, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 1011)
        - Negative Numbers 2511 to 2524, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 1012-1025)
        - Negative Number 2526, printed 2005 June (Box 21, Folder 1026)
        - Negative Numbers 3670 to 3676, printed 2005 September (Box 22, Folder 1027-1033)
        - Negative Number 3677, printed 2005 September (Box 22, Folder 1034)
          2 photographic prints, neither print matches the negative with the corresponding number in the collection.
        - Negative Numbers 3678 to 3684, printed 2005 September (Box 22, Folder 1035-1041)
        - Negative Number 3685, printed 2005 September (Box 22, Folder 1042)
        - Negative Number 3687, printed 2005 September (Box 22, Folder 1043)
        - Negative Numbers 3688 to 3708, printed 2005 September (Box 22, Folder 1044-1064)
      - Images Captured in 2008
        - Negative Number 92854, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1065)
        - Negative Numbers 94075 to 94082, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1066-1073)
        - Negative Number 94086, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1074)
        - Negative Number 94090, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1075)
        - Negative Number 94092, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1076)
        - Negative Number 94097, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1077)
        - Negative Numbers 94111 to 94113, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1078-1080)
        - Negative Number 94115, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1081)
        - Negative Number 94147, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1082)
        - Negative Numbers 94172 to 94173, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1083-1084)
        - Negative Numbers 94385 to 94386, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1085-1086)
        - Negative Number 94389, printed in 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1087)
    - Black-and-white Prints, 2003–2004
      Black-and-white photographic prints, 20.2 x 25.1 cm, on paper by an unidentified manufacturer.
      Arranged chronologically under headings for the year of image capture and then sequentially by negative number followed by undated images without negative numbers.
      - Images Captured in 2003
        - Negative Numbers 5908 to 5909, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1088-1089)
          Each folder houses 2 photographic prints.
        - Negative Numbers 6034 to 6035, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1090-1091)
        - Negative Number 6036, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1092)
        - Negative Numbers 6037 to 6039, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1093-1095)
        - Negative Number 6040, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1096)
          3 photographic prints
        - Negative Number 6041, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1097)
        - Negative Numbers 6372 to 6378, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1098-1104)
        - Negative Numbers 6418 to 6424, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1105-1111)
        - Negative Number 6426, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1112)
        - Negative Number 6429, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1113)
        - Negative Number 6431, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1114)
        - Negative Numbers 8472 to 8481, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1115-1124)
        - Negative Numbers 8835 to 8842, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1125-1132)
        - Negative Numbers 8998 to 9002, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1133-1137)
        - Negative Numbers 9004 to 9006, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1138-1140)
      - Images Captured in 2004
        - Negative Numbers 9757 to 9758, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1141-1142)
        - Negative Number 9759, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1143)
        - Negative Numbers 9761 to 9764, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1144-1147)
      - Images Without Negative Numbers
        - 4-wheeler, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1148)
        - Aspen, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1149)
        - Caution ( Sign ), printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1150)
        - Dead Cow, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1151)
          2 photographic prints
        - Flag Reflect, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1152)
        - Herder 1 with Dog, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1153)
        - Herder 2, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1154)
        - Hill, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1155)
        - Pic Reflect, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1156)
        - Sheep Herder 1, printed in 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1157)
  - Color Transparencies, circa 2006-2008
    Twenty 35-millimeter color transparencies in plastic mounts and housed in a single sheet that reproduce images created by Laura McPhee during her residency in the Sawtooth Valley, Idaho, 2003-2008.
    - 35-millimeter color slides, circa 2006-2008 (Box 25)
  - Negatives, 2003–2008
    Negatives for images created by Laura McPhee during her residency in the Sawtooth Valley, Idaho, 2003-2008.
    Each folder houses a single negative.
    Organized under two headings: Color Film Negatives and Black and White Negatives.
    - Color Film Negatives, 2003–2005
      Color negatives on Kodak Portra 400 Natural Color (NC) film, 20.2 x 25.3 cm.
      - Images Captured in 2003
        - Negative Numbers 5962 to 5971, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1158-1167)
        - Negative Number 6000, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1168)
        - Negative Number 6000, Varient 1, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1169)
        - Negative Number 6022, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1170)
        - Negative Number 6022, Varient 1, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1171)
        - Negative Numbers 6023, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1172)
        - Negative Numbers 6025 to 6029, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1173-1177)
        - Negative Number 6033, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1178)
        - Negative Numbers 6047 to 6051, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1179-1183)
        - Negative Number 6110, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1184)
        - Negative Number 6110, Varient 1, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1185)
        - Negative Number 6110, Varient 2, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1186)
        - Negative Number 6111, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1187)
        - Negative Numbers 6113 to 6123, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1188-1198)
        - Negative Numbers 6253 to 6254, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1199-1200)
        - Negative Numbers 6540 to 6541, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1201-1202)
        - Negative Number 6542, 2003 June 21 (Box 26, Folder 1203)
        - Negative Numbers 6543 to 6548, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1204-1209)
        - Negative Numbers 6550 to 6553, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1210-1213)
        - Negative Numbers 6574 to 6575, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1214-1215)
        - Negative Numbers 6578 to 6580, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1216-1218)
        - Negative Number 6583, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1219)
        - Negative Number 6584-1520, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1220)
        - Negative Number 6587, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1221)
        - Negative Number 6589, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1222)
        - Negative Number 6591, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1223)
        - Negative Number 6591, Varient 1, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1224)
        - Negative Numbers 6597 to 6604, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1225-1232)
        - Negative Numbers 6606 to 6608, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1233-1235)
        - Negative Number 7545, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1236)
        - Negative Number 7549, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1237)
        - Negative Numbers 7551 to 7556, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1238-1243)
        - Negative Numbers 7558 to 7559, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1244-1245)
        - Negative Numbers 7602 to 7615, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1246-1259)
        - Negative Numbers 7754 to 7763, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1260-1269)
        - Negative Number 7821, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1270)
        - Negative Numbers 7853 to 7865, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1271-1283)
        - Negative Numbers 7890 to 7899, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1284-1293)
        - Negative Numbers 7902 to 7909, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1294-1301)
        - Negative Numbers 8001 to 8002, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1302-1303)
        - Negative Numbers 8004 to 8013, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1304-1313)
        - Negative Numbers 8015 to 8016, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1314-1315)
        - Negative Number 8018, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1316)
        - Negative Numbers 8020 to 8034, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1317-1331)
        - Negative Number 8036, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1332)
        - Negative Numbers 8038 to 8039, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1333-1334)
        - Negative Numbers 8043 to 8044, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1335-1336)
        - Negative Number 8047, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1337)
        - Negative Numbers 8059 to 8060, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1338-1339)
        - Negative Numbers 8074 to 8078, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1340-1344)
      - Images Captured in 2004
        - Negative Numbers 9555 to 9574, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1345-1364)
        - Negative Number 9609, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1365)
        - Negative Numbers 9633 to 9651, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1366-1384)
        - Negative Numbers 9653 to 9655, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1385-1387)
        - Negative Numbers 9657 to 9660, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1388-1391)
        - Negative Numbers 9722 to 9726, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1392-1396)
        - Negative Numbers 9728 to 9731, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1397-1400)
        - Negative Numbers 9733 to 9739, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1401-1407)
        - Negative Numbers 9741 to 9750, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1408-1417)
        - Negative Numbers 9752 to 9756, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1418-1422)
        - Negative Numbers 9766 to 9783, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1423-1440)
        - Negative Numbers 9785 to 9788, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1441-1444)
        - Negative Numbers 9792 to 9794, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1445-1447)
        - Negative Numbers 9808 to 9809, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1448-1449)
        - Negative Numbers 1890 to 1892, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1450-1452)
        - Negative Numbers 3166 to 3170, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1453-1457)
        - Negative Numbers 4001 to 4007, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1458-1464)
        - Negative Numbers 6340 to 6357, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1465-1482)
        - Negative Number 6379, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1483)
        - Negative Number 6380, 2004 July 15 (Box 29, Folder 1484)
        - Negative Numbers 6381 to 6383, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1485-1487)
        - Negative Numbers 6385 to 6441, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1488-1544)
        - Negative Numbers 6448 to 6452, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1545-1549)
        - Negative Numbers 6454 to 6468, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1550-1564)
        - Negative Numbers 6471 to 6475, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1565-1569)
        - Negative Numbers 6478 to 6505, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1570-1597)
        - Negative Numbers 6507 to 6521, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1598-1612)
        - Negative Numbers 6523 to 6536, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1613-1626)
        - Negative Number 6584, 2004 July 8 (Box 29, Folder 1627)
        - Negative Numbers 6585 to 6587, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 1628-1630)
        - Negative Numbers 2912 to 2929, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1631-1648)
        - Negative Number 2932, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1649)
        - Negative Numbers 2935 to 2936, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1650-1651)
        - Negative Numbers 2938 to 2941, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1652-1655)
        - Negative Numbers 2943 to 2944, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1656-1657)
        - Negative Number 2951, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1658)
        - Negative Numbers 2954 to 2958, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1659-1663)
        - Negative Numbers 2961 to 2967, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1664-1670)
        - Negative Numbers 2969 to 2973, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1671-1675)
        - Negative Numbers 2975 to 2984, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1676-1685)
        - Negative Numbers 2986 to 2987, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1686-1687)
        - Negative Number 2989, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1688)
        - Negative Numbers 2992 to 2993, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1689-1690)
        - Negative Number 2995, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1691)
        - Negative Numbers 2998 to 3012, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1692-1706)
        - Negative Numbers 3014 to 3022, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1707-1715)
      - Images Captured in 2005
        - Negative Numbers 626 to 633, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 1716-1723)
        - Negative Numbers 636 to 639, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 1724-1727)
        - Negative Numbers 641 to 674, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 1728-1761)
        - Negative Number 677, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 1762)
        - Negative Numbers 680 to 684, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 1763-1767)
        - Negative Numbers 686 to 698, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 1768-1780)
        - Negative Numbers 710 to 720, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 1781-1791)
        - Negative Numbers 2070 to 2079, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1792-1801)
        - Negative Numbers 2080 to 2081, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1802-1803)
        - Negative Numbers 2083 to 2084, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1804-1805)
        - Negative Numbers 2086 to 2096, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1806-1816)
        - Negative Number 2097, 2005 May (Box 32, Folder 1817)
        - Negative Number 2098, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1818)
        - Negative Number 2099, 2005 March (Box 32, Folder 1819)
        - Negative Numbers 2100 to 2104, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1820-1824)
        - Negative Numbers 2106 to 2109, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1825-1828)
        - Negative Numbers 2111 to 2127, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1829-1845)
        - Negative Numbers 2129 to 2134, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1846-1851)
        - Negative Number 2135, 2005 May 31 (Box 32, Folder 1852)
        - Negative Numbers 2139 to 2140, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1853-1854)
        - Negative Numbers 2142 to 2147, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1855-1860)
        - Negative Number 2148, 2005 May (Box 32, Folder 1861)
        - Negative Number 2508, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1862)
        - Negative Numbers 2511 to 2524, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1863-1876)
        - Negative Number 2526, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 1877)
        - Negative Numbers 3670 to 3685, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 1878-1893)
        - Negative Numbers 3687 to 3709, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 1894-1916)
      - Images Captured in 2008
        - Negative Number 92854, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 1917)
        - Negative Numbers 94075 to 94082, 2007–2008 (Box 34, Folder 1918-1925)
        - Negative Number 94086, 2007–2008 (Box 34, Folder 1926)
        - Negative Number 94090, 2008 January 27 (Box 34, Folder 1927)
        - Negative Number 94092, 2007–2008 (Box 34, Folder 1928)
        - Negative Number 94097, 2007–2008 (Box 34, Folder 1929)
        - Negative Numbers 94111 to 94113, 2007–2008 (Box 34, Folder 1930-1932)
        - Negative Number 94115, 2007–2008 (Box 34, Folder 1933)
        - Negative Number 94147, 2007–2008 (Box 34, Folder 1934)
        - Negative Numbers 94172 to 94173, 2007–2008 (Box 34, Folder 1935-1936)
        - Negative Numbers 94385 to 94386, 2007–2008 (Box 34, Folder 1937-1938)
        - Negative Number 94389, 2007–2008 (Box 34, Folder 1939)
    - Black-and-white Film Negatives, 2003–2004
      Black-and-white film negatives, 20.2 x 25.4 cm, on Kodak Tri-X Pan Professional 4164 film.
      - Images Captured in 2003
        - Negative Numbers 5908 to 5909, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 1940-1941)
        - Negative Numbers 6034 to 6041, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 1942-1949)
        - Negative Numbers 6372 to 6378, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 1950-1956)